{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/3447","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3447","name":"Detroit Community Schools","address":"12675  Burt Rd.","zipcode":"48223","owner":"Detroit Board of Education","licenseNumber":"250431","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.24736,42.38018","geojson":{"id":"3447","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.247361232,42.38017985]},"properties":{"name":"Detroit Community Schools","owner":"Detroit Board of Education","address":"12675  Burt Rd.","zipcode":"48223","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"250431","establishmentid":"3447","establishment_type":"Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"2022-04-26"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"2254","name":"DON'S VENDING SERVICE","address":"12675 BURT RD","zipcode":"48219"},{"establishmentid":"1753","name":"Vix Vending","address":"12400 Burt","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"2193","name":"Robinson Dairy Vending","address":"12400 Burt","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"4548","name":"Vix Vending","address":"12400 Burt Rd.","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1033","name":"Gompers Elementary School","address":"20601 Davison Ave. W.","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"991","name":"Rouge Park Golf Course","address":"11701 Burt Rd.","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"51623905","name":"Lee's Eat Up Cafe","address":"21306 Schoolcraft","zipcode":"48223"},{"establishmentid":"4285","name":"City Mission","address":"20405 Schoolcraft Rd.","zipcode":"48223"},{"establishmentid":"51623795","name":"Plymouth Coney Island","address":"20804 Plymouth","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"2452","name":"Mary's Grill #1","address":"20804 Plymouth Rd.","zipcode":"48228"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"60986","inspectionDate":"2022-12-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"59240","inspectionDate":"2022-04-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Reach-in Freezer","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-04-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-501.11","violationDescription":"Stored frozen FOODS shall be maintained frozen.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Frozen food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not frozen solid","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Reach-in Freezer","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Reach-in Freezer","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"56316","inspectionDate":"2021-10-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"55101","inspectionDate":"2021-06-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SINKS","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"53593","inspectionDate":"2020-12-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-206.12","violationDescription":"Rodent bait shall be contained in a covered, tamper-resistant bait station. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Rodent bait station(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not covered","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-06-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink kitchen","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-06-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"53109","inspectionDate":"2020-10-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Closed - Attempt ins","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51240","inspectionDate":"2020-03-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"49345","inspectionDate":"2019-10-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"SINKS","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-10-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"SINKS","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-10-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SINKS","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-10-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"47788","inspectionDate":"2019-05-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-05-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"43813","inspectionDate":"2018-10-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall/ceiling covering(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."}]},{"inspectionid":"42104","inspectionDate":"2018-05-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall/ceiling covering(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."}]},{"inspectionid":"40031","inspectionDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall/ceiling covering(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."}]},{"inspectionid":"38649","inspectionDate":"2017-05-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"36566","inspectionDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3447"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}